<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>geo on Greentechdev</title>
    <link>/tags/geo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in geo on Greentechdev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/geo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Naturvårdsregistret, NVR</title>
      <link>/data/nvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data/nvr/</guid>
      <description>Naturvårdsregistret (NVR) Data from the official list of protected nature areas (sites) in Sweden (Naturvårdsregistret, NVR) is exposed through a number of distribution channels.
Read more about protected nature areas:
 http://www.swedishepa.se/Enjoying-nature/Protected-areas/ http://www.naturvardsverket.se/Var-natur/Skyddad-natur/ (Swedish) http://www.naturvardsverket.se/Sa-mar-miljon/Kartor/Kartverktyget-Skyddad-natur/ (Swedish)  Data quality See the Swedish EPA&amp;rsquo;s metadata catalogue for details: Öppna tjänster för data i naturvårdsregistret (Swedish).
License &amp;amp; conditions The data is licensed under Creative Commons Zero, CC0.  Our APIs and data are provided &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trails and devices in outdoor life</title>
      <link>/data/trails-and-devices-in-outdoor-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data/trails-and-devices-in-outdoor-life/</guid>
      <description>Trails and devices in outdoor life Trails and devices (e.g. toilets, parking lots) in national parks or other nature areas.
Data quality See the Swedish EPA&amp;rsquo;s metadata catalogue for details: Friluftsliv: Leder och anordningar i skyddade områden (Swedish).
License &amp;amp; conditions The data is licensed under Creative Commons Zero, CC0.  Our APIs and data are provided &#34;as is&#34; without guarantees concerning potential errors in the data, availability and performance of the API and similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air quality measurements</title>
      <link>/data/air-quality-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data/air-quality-measurements/</guid>
      <description>Air quality measurements Near real-time national air quality data from measuring stations - the air quality data provides information on the levels of various air pollutants, including particles, nitrogen dioxide and ground-level ozone, in Swedish cities and in rural areas. The data is made available via a HTTP/REST API with various usage examples.
The data is provided in cooperation with SMHI.
See Luftkvaliteten i realtid och preliminär statistik for more information (Swedish).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>